(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) George's best friend was visiting him.
Joseph lived in Arizona.
George moved to Los Angeles two years ago.
He hadn't seen Joseph since then.
George wanted his friend to have fun.
He wanted to convince him to move to
Los Angeles with him.
George had a great idea.
He would take his friend to Six Flags.
They didn't have big roller coasters in Arizona.
George and Joseph got on a ride called
Tatsu.
It was huge and had more than five
loops.
Joseph screamed more than any other people.
Isn't that great, asked George.
If you move here, we'll be coming here
all the time.
Joseph never returned to Los Angeles again.